footballguys.com 2015-04-07

# Money Back Guarantee

Last Updated: 8/15/2009

Footballguys.com is dedicated to providing all the fantasy football information that you need to DOMINATE YOUR LEAGUE. We're constantly working on new features and tools to keep you, our subscribers, better informed. We also realize that privacy is a very important issue to our site visitors and subscribers. This Privacy Policy details what type of information we collect on our visitors and how it is used.

**Personally Identifying Information**

We collect the Personally Identifying Information listed below:

  * **Signing Up For Subscriber Site:** When purchasing a subscription from Footballguys, we ask for your name, an email address, a username, and a password. We also store the IP address that the subscription request came from for security. We only collect information on your physical address if you order a product that requires that we ship it to you by mail. We do not collect or retain any payment information such as credit card numbers, bank account numbers or PINs -- our payment processor (currently PayPal) handles this for us. The only payment information we retain is the receipt number on the transaction that our payment processor sends to us.

  * **Signing Up For Message Board:** When registering for the Footballguys Message Board, we ask for a username, a password, an email address, and your time zone. We also store the IP address that the registration request was made from so that we can detect and manage duplicate accounts. We do not require any other information to set up a message board account.

  * **Logging In To Subscriber Site:** When you log in to the Subscriber Site, we ask for your login and password. We also collect your IP address so that we can extract and analyze demographic data about our subscribers.

  * **Logging In To Message Board:** When you log in to the Message Board, we ask for your Message Board login and password. No other information is stored when you log in to the Message Board.

  * **Using The Subscriber Site:** Each time you access Subscriber Content, we record your login and IP address. We record this information so that we can determine how popular each of our tools and features are and so that we can detect login sharing.

  * **Using the Message Board:** Each time you post a new topic, reply to an existing topic, or vote in a poll on the message board, your username, IP address, and the content of your topic, reply, or vote are stored in our database. We store this data because it provides the content of the Message Board itself and the identity of the user who created it.

**Cookies**

  * Footballguys uses cookies to recognize and remember the identities of our registered users so that they do not have to log in each time they return to the site. We also use cookies on our Message Board to store some user preferences such as the number of messages or topics to display on a page, topics already read, etc. A "cookie" is a small text file containing letters or numbers that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. Most browsers accept cookies by default. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to alert you when a cookie is being sent. However, some Footballguys features or services may not function correctly if cookies cannot be set to your browser.

**Information sharing**

  * We do not provide, rent, or sell any of your personally identifying information to other companies or individuals.
  * If you have an account, we may share the information submitted under your account among all of our services in order to provide you with a seamless experience and to improve the quality of our services. We will not disclose your account information to other people or non-affiliated companies.
  * We may store and process personal information collected on our site in the United States or any other country in which Sportsguys, LLC. or its agents maintain facilities. By using our services, you consent to the transfer of your information among these facilities, including those located outside your country.
  * In the event of a transfer of ownership of Sportsguys, LLC., such as acquisition by or merger with another company, we will provide notice before any personally identifying information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.
  * We may share aggregated information with others. Examples of this include how many users clicked on a particular advertisement. We will not provide the individual identities of users in this case.

**Information security**

  * We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data.
  * We provide access to your personally identifying information only to a minimum number of our employees who need to know that information in order to provide service to our customers or develop and improve our services.

**Updating your information**

  * We provide webpages where you may update and correct your personally identifying information. On our Message Boards, click on the "My Controls" link for more information. On our Subscriber Site, visit [this](http://www.footballguys.com/amember/profile.php) page.

**External links**

  * Any external sites linked from pages on Footballguys.com are created and maintained by people and companies we have no control over. These other sites are not bound by our Privacy Policy and they may have different policies regarding the collection of personal information, cookies, etc.

**Email updates**

  * Footballguys.com does not send unsolicited mail. We send news updates during the offseason to people who subscribe to our offseason mailing list. During the season, we send selected content and breaking news updates to our subscribers by email. If you do not wish to receive these messages, you can unsubscribe from the mailing list by clicking on the unsubscribe link in the email, by visiting [this page](http://www.footballguys.com/dailyemailunsubscribe.php), or by sending an email to [subscription@footballguys.com](mailto:subscription@footballguys.com?subject=Email%20Unsubscribe).
  * We do not share the membership list of our mailing lists with anyone.

**Our Commitment To Children's Privacy**

  * Footballguys.com believes that it is particularly important to protect the privacy of children. For that reason, we do not collect or maintain information at our web sites from those we actually know are under the age of 13, and no part of our web site is structured to attract anyone under the age of 13.

**Changes to this Policy**

  * Our Privacy Policy will change from time to time as we expand our services to our subscribers. We believe that most changes will be minor, but there may be more substantial changes at some point in the future. In any case, we will post those changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will also provide a more prominent notification of the change. We will place the effective date of each Privacy Policy at the top of this page. Prior versions of this Privacy Policy will be kept in an archive for you to view.

**Privacy Policy Archive**

  *  Effective date: 3/21/2009

If you have any additional questions, please feel free to contact us at any time.   
Footballguys.com  
PO Box 937  
Cabot, AR 72023-0937
